travelervip.com 2014-05-26

# Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy Does Matter to Us**

As you would expect from all the hand-picked properties showcased in our on our website, Traveler|VIP respects your privacy and will take all reasonable measures to protect it. We will not sell, share, rent, or otherwise provide any personal information you have given us, to any third party without your permission.

Traveler|VIP will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Our servers collect data each time a user navigates our site. This information is anonymous in nature and includes such information as the number, frequency and duration of each visit, as well as details about click-through to our hotel sites and other third party sites. We will share this non-personal, aggregate, or summary information with partners or other third parties, but Traveler|VIP will not sell or share any information at the individual level.

All personal information you do give us will be used exclusively by Traveler|VIP to communicate directly with you, or with the hotels displayed on our website, for the purpose of arranging your hotel bookings or answering questions about a booking. Any information you give us will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. At any time you may ask us to discontinue use of the information you have provided, and request that we refrain from sending any further communications to you via that information, by simply sending us a request at info@travelervip.com. Traveler|VIP commits to accept and abide by such a request immediately.

We do reserve the right to change this policy as we expand or alter our services. Accordingly we recommend that you check from time to time in order to understand how we treat your personal information. Your use of this website and its services constitute your agreement to the terms of our privacy policy. If we change those policies, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your continued use of this website and its services constitute your agreement to any such changes.

If you have any questions or concerns feel free to email us.
